-[Uzi]: 'Sup, losers??
Uzi here!
Ready to yell and break stuff!
[cackles]
-[Pomni]: [uninspired]
And me.
Pomni.
Your favorite mentally sound jester.
-[Uzi]: Today is BLACK FRIDAY!!!!
Or, was it yesterday?
Uh, I-I dunno what day it is.
-[Pomni]: As such, we've got some...
super cute items for you.
-[Uzi]: "Cute items"?
Try MEGA KILLER DEATH ITEMS!!
[cackling]
[thunder crashes]
Tremble helplessly
before this sick-as-hell N statue!
What could be more awesome?
-[N]: "Go Fish" is pretty awesome!
[thunder crashes]
-[Pomni]: Uhhh, that's cool.
But w-w-wait till you see
OUR big-ticket item!
[inhales sharply]
[whispering]
Caine, what's our big-ticket item?
[shwing!]
-[Uzi]: It happens.
-[Pomni]: CAINE!!
I want my [doink!] thumbs back!
You'd better not make me run
on that wheely thing or --
or -- or make me stuff my cheeks
with those little rat pellets!
-[Uzi]: Can you pause your breakdown
and finish your script?
I don't have all day.
-[Pomni]: [inhales sharply]
Do you have any idea how humiliating this is?
Get me a tiny phone!
I need to call somebody!
This is ridiculous!
And what's with this constant urge to dig?
-[Uzi]: [sighs]
I've gotta do everything, don't I?
Uh, for this Black Friday,
we got some, uh, dangerous,
killer Digital Circus items for you!
Born of ancient horrors and gelatin,
this squishy beast wants nothing more
than to MURDER YOUR WHOLE FAMILY
IN COLD BLOOD!!!
-[Gummigoo]:
A bit of an exaggeration there, mate.
But I am squishy.
-[Pomni]: [sobbing]
I don't want to be a hamster!
I don't want to be a hamster!!
[whack!]
Ow.
Okay, okay.
Uh, what is this?
We got a...
Murder Drones mat?
It's definitely not cute.
It's, uh...
scary.
And... death.
Yeah, totally wouldn't use this
to play cute farming games with.
-[Uzi]: We beheaded a rabbit
and turned it into a BAG!
The perfect place to hide
all your AGONY and ANGST!!!
And here?
The rabbit's son.
Wide-eyed and trembling...
watching as you fashionably strut around
with his DAD'S HEAD!!!
-[Jax]: Eh, still beats
Caine's dumb adventures.
-[Caine]: You're a dumb adventure!
-[Jax]: AGH!
-[Pomni]:
And then, there's this...
...terrifying, nasty-looking robot statue thing.
-[N]: [heartbroken]
You... think I'm... nasty?
-[Pomni]: Yes. I mean, n-no!
-[N]: [sobbing]
-[Pomni]: I meant, like...
in a -- in a nasty,
g-gritty metal...
bodacious sort of way?
-[N]: [cheerful]
Oh, cool! Okay!
[chuckles]
I'm not actually a statue, by the way.
I'm just standing veeeery still,
and it hurts so bad!
-[Uzi]: And, available only
for a limited time,
this vinyl spins with
the tortured wails of the damned.
Each note a scream of despair!
[cheerful, goofy music plays]
Hell incarnate.
Available only for a limited time.
-[N]: [chuckles] And that's why you should
never drink a giraffe's milk after Christmas!
-[Pomni]: [laughing nervously]
Hey, look!
-[Uzi]: Huh?? [wails]
-[Pomni]:
A cute and cuddly robot plushie
perfect for snuggling on chilly nights.
-[Uzi]: Wait!
Y-You think I'm cute and cuddly?
UGH, that's super cringe!
What are you trying to do --
ruin my brand?!
-[Pomni]: I was just saying --
-[Uzi]: I cant have my fans thinking
I'm some soft-shelled taco like you!
-[Pomni]: Did you fall out of bed
on the wrong side this morning?
Or did someone spike your coffee
with crybaby pills?!
-[Uzi]: How about I --
-[Pomni]: You're literally being
a squishy baby right now!
-[Uzi]: You know what?
Shut up!
-[Pomni]: YOU shut up!
-[Uzi]: You shut up!
-[Pomni]: You shut up!
-[Uzi]: Ugh! You shut up!
-[Pomni]: I'm not shutting up,
and I'm done talking to you!
-[Uzi]: Shut up!
-[Pomni]: La-la-la-la-la --
-[Uzi]: I'm done. I'm done with this.
-[Pomni]: I cant hear anything you're saying!!
I'm calling my lawyer!!
La-la-la-la-la!
[door opens, slams shut]
La-la-la-la-la!!!
Can I be turned back to normal now?
[shwing!]